

Personal Info

4 +40 768 708 522

alexandru.nedelcu.office@gmail.com

Bucharest, Romania

Links

- ➤ <u>Linkedin</u>
- ➤ <u>GitHub</u>
- > Portfolio

Skills

- Python
- HTML & CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- Git & Control Version
- WordPress & Elementor
- Interpersonal skills
- Collaboration skills
- Chrome DevTools
- Jira System
- Office & Google Workspace
- Adobe Photoshop
- Graphic Design
- Team management

Languages

- English
- Русский
- Romanian

Proactive and passionate **software developer** with experience in creating, improving, and completing web applications and projects, with a background in **web design**, E-commerce, custom brand graphics, and marketing. Focused on streamlining, optimizing, and managing processes. I look for opportunities to grow, connect to people, and develop my skills. Also interested in automation and data analysis. Always learning and having fun.

Work Experience

Technical Support Specialist (remote), Valoris

July 2023

- Technical support for software issues and troubleshooting problems in the Kyocera Document Solutions project.
- Working with clients from the Porsche Group Romania (porsche, audi, skoda, lamborghini, wv, bentley etc.)

QA Game Tester, Greenlink

Oct 2022 - Nov 2022

- Collaborated on a small project with a team of testers to identify, isolate and report bugs. Using Jira to accurately document, track and report issues found during testing.
- Created detailed reports and personally collaborated directly with developers to identify potential areas of improvement.

Customer Relations Agent, IQBox

2021 - 2022

- Generated ~44%+ more sales than the average employee every month, through optimising work and a more effective approach.
- Trained a team of 5 people with ~38% more sales than the average.
- Specialist in the representative company's team meetings regarding the big change of the company's Telecom partner to Vodafone in 2021.
- Personally implemented more effective low-end target strategies in the department.
- Proficient in data entry, CRM systems and document management.

Web Designer Freelancer

2020 - 2021

- Designed and developed E-commerce websites and landing pages with Wordpress and Elementor.
- Integrated Facebook Pixel Analytics for sales and leads tracking.
- Maintained and administered websites, including updating contents and improving user experience.
- Experience in troubleshooting and debugging issues related to website design, user data, gdpr, chat, payment and translation.

Education and Courses

- Complete Web Developer, Studioweb
- Python Basic, Step IT
- Business Finance and Entrepreneurship, Dalles GO

Backup links:

- https://www.linkedin.com/in/alexandru-nedelcu-office/
- ➤ https://github.com/UmbraNova
- https://umbranova.github.io/My-Portfolio-Project/